<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Joe&#39;s Portfolio</title>
    <link>https://cyberpirate.github.io/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Joe&#39;s Portfolio</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2017 15:24:41 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://cyberpirate.github.io/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>iSpeech-Speech-Recognition-ASR-Voice-Recognition.js</title>
      <link>https://cyberpirate.github.io/post/ispeech-speech-recognition-asr-voice-recognition.js/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2017 15:24:41 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cyberpirate.github.io/post/ispeech-speech-recognition-asr-voice-recognition.js/</guid>
      <description>Goal This SDK is designed to enable developers to interact with the Voice Recognition iSpeech API using Javascript.
Implementation The SDK uses getUserMedia() to record audio from the browser, encodes it to speex, then streams the data to the iSpeech API using a WebSocket.
Completed This project completed the stated goals.
My contribution I developed and maintained this project through its lifecycle, along with providing tech support where needed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>iSpeech-Text-to-Speech-TTS-Speech-Synthesis.js</title>
      <link>https://cyberpirate.github.io/post/ispeech-text-to-speech-tts-speech-synthesis.js/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2017 15:24:26 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cyberpirate.github.io/post/ispeech-text-to-speech-tts-speech-synthesis.js/</guid>
      <description>Goal This SDK is designed to enable developers to interact with the Text to Speech iSpeech API using Javascript.
Implementation This SDK uses HTML5 &amp;lt;audio&amp;gt; tags to play synthesized text in the browser.
Completed This SDK completed its stated goals.
My contribution I developed and maintained this project through its lifecycle, along with providing tech support where needed.
Source Code</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>iSpeech-Android-SDK</title>
      <link>https://cyberpirate.github.io/post/ispeech-android-sdk/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2017 15:23:41 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cyberpirate.github.io/post/ispeech-android-sdk/</guid>
      <description>Goal The goal of this project was to create an open source Android SDK to help customers access the API quickly and easily.
Implementation For Speech Recognition the SDK uses the Android system to record WAV audio, converts it to Speex, and streams that audio to the server in real time for recognition.
For Text to Speech the SDK accesses iSpeech&amp;rsquo;s REST api and streams the audio.
Completed The SDK accomplishes the stated goals and is being maintained.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>jailUserManager.py</title>
      <link>https://cyberpirate.github.io/post/jailusermanager.py/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2017 15:23:23 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cyberpirate.github.io/post/jailusermanager.py/</guid>
      <description>Goal Fix incorrect permissions on mounted files in FreeNAS and add relevant users/groups to any jails that need access to files.
Implementation This python script scans the configured folders for incorrect permissions and fixes them. It also scans any jails for missing users/groups and adds them if neccessary.
Completed  Scans for incorrect permissions Scans for missing users in jails  Future goals None yet
Source Code</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PersonalChina</title>
      <link>https://cyberpirate.github.io/post/personalchina/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2017 15:23:16 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cyberpirate.github.io/post/personalchina/</guid>
      <description>Goal The goal of this project is to ensure that any software on my system can not phone home without my express approval.
Implementation This project configures VyOS firewall rules to create a whitelist that the firewall uses to filter traffic.
Completed  rule configuration command line interface expiring rules  Future goals  web interface blocked request log  Source Code</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DataStoreLib.py</title>
      <link>https://cyberpirate.github.io/post/datastorelib.py/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2017 15:03:41 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cyberpirate.github.io/post/datastorelib.py/</guid>
      <description>Goal DataStoreLib.py is a python SDK designed to access the DataStore API.
Implementation DataStoreLib.py simplifies the DataStore API into two python functions
#file: file to be passed to requests #mimeType: string mimeType #data: dictionary of metadata for the file DataStore.uploadFile(file, mimeType, data) #returns: True or False #conditions: array of conditions to pass to DataStore. # Syntax in the DataStore documentation DataStore.getIds(conditions) #returns: array of urls to files passing the conditions  Completed  Uploading Files Searching Metadata  Future goals None yet</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DataStore</title>
      <link>https://cyberpirate.github.io/post/datastore/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2017 14:36:27 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cyberpirate.github.io/post/datastore/</guid>
      <description>Goal DataStore is designed to store many small files with metadata attached to each file. This metadata could be searched later to download the files that fit the search query.
Implementation DataStore is written using php for processing. MySQL is used to store and search the metadata and Apache is used to serve the uploaded files.
Completed  Uploading Files Searching Metadata Downloading Files  Future goals  Auto setup for database tables Auto backup for metadata  Source Code</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>