<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Voice Recognition on Joe&#39;s Portfolio</title>
    <link>http://www.joei.tech/tags/voice-recognition/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Voice Recognition on Joe&#39;s Portfolio</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <managingEditor>joe.v.iacoviello@gmail.com (Joseph Iacoviello)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>joe.v.iacoviello@gmail.com (Joseph Iacoviello)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 05 Jul 2015 12:00:00 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.joei.tech/tags/voice-recognition/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>DriveSafe.ly</title>
      <link>http://www.joei.tech/post/drivesafe.ly/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jul 2015 12:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>joe.v.iacoviello@gmail.com (Joseph Iacoviello)</author>
      <guid>http://www.joei.tech/post/drivesafe.ly/</guid>
      <description>Goal The goal of this project was to help prevent people from driving dangerously by reading text messages to them and allowing them to respond with their voice.
Implementation The app uses the iSpeech api to recognize the user&amp;rsquo;s voice and to speak any texts or emails the user receives.
Completed The app accomplishes the stated goals and is being maintained.
My contribution The app was written when I joined the team, I was responsible for updating it for new android versions and maintaining it, taking user feedback into account.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Talkz, Celebrity Voice changer</title>
      <link>http://www.joei.tech/post/talkz/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2015 12:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>joe.v.iacoviello@gmail.com (Joseph Iacoviello)</author>
      <guid>http://www.joei.tech/post/talkz/</guid>
      <description>Goal The goal of this project was to create an entertaining app where users can edit their voice to sound like a celebrity.
Implementation The app uses the Hats Off Api to stream audio to their servers, then play the processed results.
Completed The app accomplishes the stated goals and is being maintained.
My contribution I contributed to this app from it&amp;rsquo;s creation, and helped maintain it through it&amp;rsquo;s lifecycle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>iSpeech-Speech-Recognition-ASR-Voice-Recognition.js</title>
      <link>http://www.joei.tech/post/ispeech-speech-recognition-asr-voice-recognition.js/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Apr 2015 12:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>joe.v.iacoviello@gmail.com (Joseph Iacoviello)</author>
      <guid>http://www.joei.tech/post/ispeech-speech-recognition-asr-voice-recognition.js/</guid>
      <description>Goal This SDK is designed to enable developers to interact with the Voice Recognition iSpeech API using Javascript.
Implementation The SDK uses getUserMedia() to record audio from the browser, encodes it to speex, then streams the data to the iSpeech API using a WebSocket.
Completed This project completed the stated goals.
My contribution I developed and maintained this project through its lifecycle, along with providing tech support where needed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>iSpeech-Android-SDK</title>
      <link>http://www.joei.tech/post/ispeech-android-sdk/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2014 12:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>joe.v.iacoviello@gmail.com (Joseph Iacoviello)</author>
      <guid>http://www.joei.tech/post/ispeech-android-sdk/</guid>
      <description>Goal The goal of this project was to create an open source Android SDK to help customers access the API quickly and easily.
Implementation For Speech Recognition the SDK uses the Android system to record WAV audio, converts it to Speex, and streams that audio to the server in real time for recognition.
For Text to Speech the SDK accesses iSpeech&amp;rsquo;s REST api and streams the audio.
Completed The SDK accomplishes the stated goals and is being maintained.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>